-♪ Sheldon and his brain... ♪
-Definitely better before.
(Howard:)So, I'm almost done
writing the song for Bernadette.
(Howard:)Are you cool playing the cello?
If by "cool"
you mean "willing to," yes.
If by "cool" you mean "cool,"
(Leonard:)clearly you've never seen me
play the cello.
(Howard:)Great. Will you play the ukulele?
(Raj:)Of course. I'd be happy
to shred it on my ax.
(Howard:)Or you could just play your tiny,
ridiculous guitar.
(Raj:)Fine. I will melt her heart.
And her face!
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen.
(Sheldon:)No doubt you heard
about my little breakthrough.
(Sheldon:)Now, if your plan
is to hoist me on your shoulders
(Sheldon:)and carry me around the cafeteria,
please refrain.
(Sheldon:)I don't care for heights,
motion sickness
(Sheldon:)or the thought of your necks
touching my buttocks.
(Howard:)Seriously, congratulations, Sheldon.
(Raj:)Yeah, I read your paper online.